Sherab GYATSO



DEVELOPER | POWERCODERS PARTICIPANT

PROFILE

I was a developer with over 3 years of experience. I have developed websites and applications that address the needs of organizations using GitHub, docker containers and hosting on-premises as well as in the AWS and Azure cloud. Currently I am transitioning to a career in the field of AWS cloud computing. I am a reliable, fast learner, passionate and committed to every project I work on.

CONTACT

10.12.1986

✓ sherab.gyatso@powercoders.org

+41 77 909 92 39

♥c/o Kant, Unterkunft AS

Zurzacherstrasse 223 5200 Brugg AG



LinkedIn-Link Portfolio-Link GitHub-Link

LANGUAGES

Tibetan **Mother Tongue**

English C1 German A1 Hindi B2

REFERENCES

Romain Geiser. Lead Company Relations AWS

romain.geiser@powercoders.org +41 78 609 08 88

HOBBIES

BASKETBALL

I really love playing basketball. It helps me to make new friends and teach me about being a good team player.

VIDEO GAMES

I like playing FIFA and squad gaming. This game has given me joy, mental stimulation and stress relief.

IT SKILLS

Advanced Intermediate **Beginner**

HTML, CSS, PHP, MYSQL DATABASE, WORDPRESS, UNIX C, C++, JAVA, JAVASCRIPT, NETWORK, SECURITY, GITHUB PYTHON, ANGULAR JS, REACT, .NET, AWS, AZURE

WORK EXPERIENCE

08/2019 - 02/2022

Developer / TCRC, Dharamsala, India

- Develop websites using wordpress framework and applications using Laravel Framework.
- Modify, update old applications and deploy them on new servers.
- Collaborate and coordinate with external developers to deploy new .NET sites on local server and mobile apps on Microsoft Azure cloud. The site URL is chatrel.net and is a pilot production in America and Canada.

06/2018 - 05/2019

Lecturer / Dalai Lama Institute (DLIHE), Bangalore, India

- Lectured for the students of Bachelor Degree and non-computer.
- Teached Mathematics for the Bachelor of Commerce students.

EDUCATION

10/2022 - 05/2023

Powercoders AWS re/Start - ICT Work Integration Program, Bern

- Preparation for a career in the AWS cloud technology by completing Cloud Practitioner Certification and Solution Architect Associate.
- Business & social skills training (team work, communication, etc.)

06/2012 - 05/2015

Master of Computer Applications / Christ University / India

Advanced knowledge in network and database management, electronics, mobile technologies, financial accounting, mathematics, statistics, cloud computing, C, C++ and Java programming. Development of an online shopping website and mobile security project as an in.

04/2009 - 04/2012

Bachelor of Computer Applications / St Joseph College / India

Fundamental understanding of C, C++, Java programming and network, database, electronics, mathematics, statistics and accounting.

VOLUNTEER EXPERIENCE

03/2016 - 04/2017

Data Analyst & Developer / Central Tibetan Administration, Dharamsala, India

Volunteer in analyzing the school data in the Education Department and developed a new database application.